Daniel Bäck

San Francisco



About

Richard hails from Tulsa. He has earned degrees from the University of Oklahoma and Stanford. (Go Sooners and Cardinals!) Before starting Pied Piper, he worked for Hooli as a part time software developer. While his work focuses on applied information theory, mostly optimizing lossless compression schema of both the length-limited and adaptive variants, his non-work interests range widely, everything from quantum computing to chaos theory. He could tell you about it, but THAT would NOT be a "length-limited" conversation!

Phone: (912) 555-4321 Email: db@sharpsrc.net

Work Experience

Facebook

Software Engineer

2014 - 2012

Give an overview of your responsibilities at the company

Increased profits by 20% from 2011-2012 through viral advertising

Education

University of Oklahoma

Information Technology, Bachelor

2011 - 2014

Skills

- Web Development
 - o HTML
 - o CSS
 - Javascript
- Compression
 - Mpeg
 - o MP4
 - o GIF

References

It is my pleasure to recommend Richard, his performance working as a consultant for Main St. Company proved that he will be a valuable addition to any company. - **Erlich Bachman**